search-snacks.com 2016-10-31

# Home - Search Snacks

**Last Updated: January 22, 2014**

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SITE OR PRODUCTS, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

**IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE SITES OR PRODUCTS.**

## Introduction

This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes how SearchSnacks LLC a Delaware Corporation (“SearchSnacks” or “we”) collects and uses the user and use information obtained through the website at searchsnacks.com (along with all subdomains, collectively, the “Site”) and the SearchSnacks products (“Products”), which are software that bring additional functionality to your web browser and computer. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site and Products.

1\. **Privacy Protection and Limitations.** We do not share your Personally-Identifiable Information with any third parties. “Personally Identifiable Information” (or “PII”) means any information that identifies or is used to determine the identity, contact information or location of an individual to whom that information pertains. PII includes, but is not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address and credit card information. Notwithstanding the above, PII does not include information that is collected anonymously (i.e., without identification of the individual user) or demographic or use information not connected to an identified individual. 

2\. **Minors.** We never knowingly collect or maintain information from those we know are under 18 years old, and no part of our Site or Products is directed at or structured to attract anyone under 18 years old. Visitors younger than 18 years of age may not use the Site or the Products.

3\. **Third Parties.** This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, nor does it apply to any other product, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. If you visit any third party websites, please review their policies carefully because they may differ substantially from our Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of any third party.

4\. **Information Collected Through Our Site**

(a)    _Traffic Data Collected_. We automatically track and collect the following categories of information when you visit our Site: (1) IP addresses; (2) domain servers; (3) types of computers accessing the Site; and (4) types of web browsers used to access the Site (collectively “Traffic Data”). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you. We use it for marketing purposes and to improve your experience on the Site.

Cookies and web beacons are very small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages. SearchSnacks collects user and use information through cookies and web beacons about your web browsing activities such as the address of the page you are visiting, the address of the referrer page you previously visited, the time you are viewing the page, your browsing environment, and your display settings. We use cookies and web beacons to:

  * Understand traffic patterns and the number of visitors to the Site and other non-SearchSnacks websites that we partner with;
  * Understand how you use and interact with the Site and/or the Products;
  * Improve our Products;
  * Optimize your experience on our Site or your use of the Products;
  * Provide non-PII auditing, research, modeling, and reporting for our advertisers and other partners;
  * Provide you relevant advertising and content; and
  * Properly manage our Site and Products.

Please note that some cookies may be placed by a third party service provider who performs some of these functions for us. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.

If you are concerned about cookies, most browsers permit individuals to decline cookies. A user refusing cookies can still fully navigate our Site and use of our Products.

(b)   _Personal Information Collected_. If you communicate with us by e-mail, such a communication identifies you personally (“Personal Information”). We keep records of your correspondence with us, but use it only for internal purposes to respond to you. If the e-mail address you provide to SearchSnacks is a wireless e-mail address, you agree to receive messages at such address from SearchSnacks (unless and until you have elected not to receive such messages by following the instructions in the unsubscribe portion of this policy). You understand that your wireless carrier’s standard rates apply to these messages. You represent that you are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges. You acknowledge having no expectation of privacy concerning Personal Information.

5. **Information Collected Through Our Products.**

  1. Our Products are available at no cost to you. Your use of them is supported through the advertising that appears when you use one of them. Our goal is to provide advertising that is relevant to you, which based upon a number of factors. We use cookies, storage data, JavaScript, web beacons, pixels, flash cookies, and other tracking technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information. Instead of identifying you personally, this information is correlated with a unique identifier that corresponds to your computing device.
  2. Our Products collect the following information, none of which specifically identifies you: IP address; a proprietary unique identifier number (derived from the type and serial number of hardware on your computer); the date and time you installed, uninstalled, and last used our product; type of operating system; type of browser; browser language, your default search service provider, search queries; browsing history; time zone, and your approximate physical location (if available). Other information that we collect depends upon the type of advertisement that is being displayed. For example, if you respond to an insurance advertisement by indicating the type of insurance you are looking for and the state in which you want the policy written for, we collect the information you provide. We use this non-personally identifiable information to improve the performance of our Products, to display advertisements that are more closely targeted to your interests, and to identify and prevent fraud. We may combine this information with information from third parties. We also share, transfer, and license this information (including your Internet search history and browsing history) to advertising partners to generate revenue, improve Product performance, and enhance the relevance of advertising you see. You acknowledge these uses of the information we gather.
  3. Our Products contain third-party software. Thus, some of the non-personally identifiable user and use information that the Products collect is sent to and used by these third parties primarily for determining which advertisement to display to you. This Privacy Policy only addresses the Products offered by us. Other websites or services have their own privacy policies regarding data collection, use and disclosure practices. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.

Please note that if you disable cookies, you will significantly degrade our ability to provide targeting advertising to you and you may also experience reduced performance of your computer and browser.

6. **User Ability to Access, Update, and Correct Personal Information**. We maintain a procedure in order to help you confirm that your Personal Information remains correct and up-to-date. At any time, you may contact SearchSnacks via email: Privacy@searchsnacks.com to update your Personal Information or request that your Personal Information no longer be shared by SearchSnacks. If you do not receive a confirmation response within 72 hours, please contact SearchSnacks again.

7\. **Security**. Most of the information we collect through our Products is not stored. We process it briefly, then remove it from our computing system. However, we do retain the proprietary unique identifier and timestamp information (date and time of install, uninstall, and last use). We use industry standard security measures (such as a firewall and password protections) to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under SearchSnacks’ control. Notwithstanding such measures, SearchSnacks cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent its computers from being illegally accessed, and the Personal Information on them stolen or altered.

8\. **Sharing with Third Party Vendors**. In addition to the uses described above, we also share, transfer, or license your user and use information to third parties to store and analyze the data, provide search results and associated advertising, provide hosting services and customer support services.

9\. **Termination and Revisions.**

  1. We reserve the right to discontinue your access to the Site or the Products at any time.
  2. We reserve the right add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site and you acknowledge that your ongoing use of the Site or Products is independent and adequate consideration in support of such modification. Without limiting the effectiveness of the foregoing, in the event of certain changes to this Privacy Policy, you may also be required to assent to the new terms, and you may also be notified by email if we have your email address. If any modification is unacceptable, your only recourse is not to use our Products and the Site.
  3. You may revoke consent at any time for any use of the Personal Information collected from you under this Privacy Policy. To revoke your consent, please indicate that decision by emailing us at support@searchsnacks.com with the word “Revoke Consent” in the subject line.

10\. **Other Privacy Issues**. If we explore a potential opportunity to sell all or part of SearchSnacks, or are otherwise involved in a merger or similar transfer of assets, we may transfer non-personally identifiable information to the other party or parties involved in the transaction. Also, we may disclose your user and use information without providing notice if we determine that disclosure is desirable to: (i) protect or defend SearchSnacks, its owners, directors, officers, employees, agents, or contractors; or (ii) comply with legal process or cooperate with a governmental investigation. The Site and our Products are hosted in the United States. You understand and consent to us transferring, processing, and storing your user and use information in the U.S. where data protection and other privacy laws may not offer the protection as where you are located.

11\. **California Privacy Rights Notice**

To request that we remove your personal information from our database, please send email to support@searchsnacks.com. You can also remove our Products by following the uninstall instructions at http://www.search-snacks.com/support/. Please note that a small file will remain on your computer after uninstalling our product. It indicates that you previously downloaded one of our products and helps us prevent fraud.
